In this short video, I show you how I
redesigned these Amazon product listing
images from Coca-Cola. Here you can see
the result. These are 100% AI generated
without any prompting, thinking or
design skills. Just needs few clicks and
couple minutes. The AI tool I used
replaced a whole creative agency and
it's changing the whole industry. Hey,
I'm Jacob. I'm founder of Scalable. Also
running a creative agency for 5 years
now and accessed my e-commerce brand
exactly 12 months ago. Now, I show you
how you can create content like this for
your brand 10 times faster and 10 times
cheaper. Stick till the end and I show
you how you can create your first three
Amazon listings for free. Let's get into
it. So, there's no skill needed anymore
to create conversion optimized content.
In this tool, you just have to paste the
asen the marketplace and select a report
language. I just used this product as a
reference here and you'd get the asen
from here. Paste it there. Select the
country and yeah the report language for
your marketplace. Start the analysis.
Now the analysis here is already
available. It takes 15 minutes and
everything will be done for you from
research from strategy then the
copywriting and also you can later do
the image generation. And when the
report is done you get all these
insights. It analyzes all your customers
from review insights the conversion
drivers. It sees what the strengths and
weaknesses of your product are and even
gives you suggestions on how to improve
your product. It rates your current
listing images and it shows you the
conversion lockers, the things that
matter to your customer but are not
properly communicated in your images.
But here I want to show you how to
create the content and to redesign their
Amazon product listing. To do this, go
to studio. On this page, the whole work
of content strategy and content brief is
done. And this is no guesswork. The
whole strategy stands on data. Here over
500 reviews got analyzed. Some
conversion blockers, customer insights,
customer benefits, and product features
got incorporated. And when you scroll
down, you'll get eight slots where you
can generate your Amazon product
listing. One for the main image and
seven for your gallery images. First of
all, I show you the current listing. And
why I picked this is because the whole
listing like the main image is not
optimized. The it's quite flat. It's
straightforward. It's quite flat, but it
lacks the emotional Christmas vibe. And
this is what I wanted to incorporate.
And yeah, for context, Coca-Cola is such
a big brand that it doesn't need any
crazy marketing on Amazon. That's why
probably for your brand, it's more
important to get optimized product
listing images that convert to make your
business grow. As you see here in the
middle, you already get the full
copyrightiting. When you double click
that, you can edit the copy and add
things or adjust to your brand tone. And
this everything will be incorporated in
the image generation. I show you a
couple of seconds. So, let's get back
here to the copy. And as you see couple
images already got generated but I show
you the exact process on how you can do
it for yourself. Now what you need to
generate these images are actually
couple clicks some references and that's
it. No thinking I already uploaded the
images and the references but I show you
how I created it. So here it's just
about yeah I used uh super quick and
dirty just the main image.
Save it here. Upload it there. There it
is.
And the brand style is important because
we want that our images incorporate the
style of our brand. Like this is how you
can stand out on Amazon with your
branding and to have consistency across
all the images. So what I did did is
actually just went on Google and picked
and screenshotted some images and pasted
them to Figma. This is what I've done.
And did a screenshot.
So let's save this up.
my tool to
back to scalable. Just upload it. It's
in the recordings. There you go.
So, and we're ready to go to click
generate.
No thinking done. It knows what to
communicate
and how to communicate it. And let's see
what will pop up here in the next
seconds.
This is it. When you compare it, I would
say it's already better. And the logic
here because Amazon has quite strict
terms of service. That's why scalable
knows that it incorporates the
information into the main image instead
of going wild with anything. But if you
want, you can edit it with this toggle
and give you a prompt and add some
badges, add something more snow and
stuff like that. You can go crazy here.
And also here's an example what I did
like going from there with the always
refreshing. Then you can really prompt
it away. No, no graphic design skills
needed. So here it disappeared. And with
the next prompt, I let the box in the
background disappear. So we only have
the can. That's about it. Just for your
understanding. Here you can set the
no-brainer mode on. It's on by default
because I don't want you to think too
much and save your energy for something
else. When you toggle this one, it
generates the images without text
overlay. This is especially important
for gallery images and uh I will show
you in a couple seconds. And then uh you
can create more images, different
formats and up to 4K. That's all about
this feature. Then when we go to the
gallery images, everything is already
set up. We can click here. I can click
here. We can click there. We can click
uh here. It already has too many. So we
can delete it. So while this is creating
where are we here? So let's wait and I
already can show you the feature because
here when you here's an example of clean
image without text. It generates
something like that that you can use for
example as a creative for or post for
social media. Here you see a similar
vibe but with this overlay from our
copier. So these are the demonstrations
and then here's some before and after.
Then the packaging and I even have to
admit this is one of the coolers. So we
have these all variations and it helps
you to become very creative and yeah I'm
not sure how much it would take to
create something like that. Just placing
the text on it and doing these renders
and stuff like that. Yeah, it saves a
lot of time. You get 10 times faster and
10 times cheaper results here. So, let
me show you real quick what it generated
in general. So, it's just clicking and
getting nice ideas and kind of Yeah,
this one is one of my favorites. And
then even some step tutorials. And then
what else do we have here? So here about
Coca-Cola
with the Christmas vip. So that's
basically it. One side note here is that
when you want to dive deeper, you have
these options. First you have the full
conversion strategy. This is built on
this is exactly your creative
strategies. This is built on all the
data, all the uh customer psychology. So
it explains you why this will convert
and you get the data foundation. You can
go back to the original beta. We go a
little bit up. The main image is mostly
prioritized with way more information.
So here the from the review insights,
the customer benefits, the products,
features are incorporated here and the
whole content brief is all already
created and you can read the primary
message what is mainly communicated to
your customer. The layout is here. So
this is something and yeah I already
mentioned the edit feature. So I think
I'm done. And here comes the goodie.
When you sign up with this link, you get
three listings for free that you can
create for your brand with the exact
same process. Thank you. I'm Jacob. If
this video gave you some value, leave a
like, leave a comment, and follow if you
want to stay upto date on this massive
AI revolution. I will share such case
studies like this on a regular basis.
face.